<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?> 
<resources> 
    <string-array name="tipps"> 
		<item>Hi, this is Scotty.\n
				I\'m the teleportation operator.
				If there is anything bugging or bothering please tell me.
				I\'ll be around to assist, help or guide you through :-)
				Just press that big button again or send me an email..\n
				So have a pleasant ride and enjoy the beam!</item>
		<item>First download some data for your area.\n
			  Go to Settings->Autocompletion \nto get offline autocompletion..</item>
		<item>Tap in the upper right corner\n
			  to set the destination you want to beam to.</item>
		<item>Tap on [start]\n
			  to set where the journey is to begin or to find out where you\'re currently at.</item>
		<item>There are a few showcase plugins available in the settings.</item>
		<item>   That\'s it :-)  </item>
		<item>There is really nothing more to do with this application for now.
			  You can find more advanced experimental versions in the redpill developer market.</item>
		<item>This button has no function other than repeating the tipps you already heard.
			  \nSet [start] and [destination] and then go beam..</item>
		<item>Have you tried switching it off and on again?</item>
		<item>So why are you still asking me?\n
			  You already know what to do.</item>
		<item>Ok one last time: Tap on [start] and/or [destination] and start beaming..</item>
		<item>I am tired of explaining this over and over again!</item>
		<item>If you don\'t like the user interface \nplease design a better one!</item>
		<item>Fork one of the git repos or mail scotty@teleportr.org what you\'d like to have..</item>
		<item>You could also edit these tipps to become more useful ;-). </item>
		<item>I\'m through. This has been my last tipp. </item>
		<item>This is the absolute final last tipp! </item>
		<item>I\'ve nothing more to tell you.</item>
		<item>There are no more tipps here!</item>
		<item>Stop pressing this button! </item>
		<item>STOP IT!!!!!!!!!!! </item>
		<item>please stop</item>
		<item>"%$@ยงX/ยง! </item>
		<item>foooo!</item>
		<item>bar?</item>
		<item>gr.</item>
		<item>Ok you get one more tipp if you promise to stop then!</item>
		<item>You just wasted 1.5 minutes of your valuable time pressing this stupid buttopn agaiun and again. You could be teleporting already. Think about it! \n:-P</item>
    </string-array> 
</resources> 